Yeah, yeah.
So yeah,
you told during recent scenario of ETL
data injection source window sourcing end
time is not given availability is there?
OK, let me give you OK.
This is the once we get the computer
start job ID and end job ID,
it gets sourcing start time from this
further starting job job run ID.
Next it gets the source job status,
source job run ID and sourcing end date
time from ETL data ingestion source
window for the ending job run ID.
It published these values into the.
So it is having the information related
to sourcing end time as well.
Yeah, sourcing end time.
So sourcing end time from ending job run
ID will be my sourcing end time.
What sourcing intent?
What happened?
We will not paste one.
So OK,
here is sourcing starting is there Now
where is the sourcing intent?
Let me show you.
I think here it wouldn't be.
For each source table it finds the active,
then cheques for the each job and if it
matches.
If it matches each L data injection
source window table will be populated
with source job and source job status and
job and time.
Yeah, as sourcing and ending time.
Yeah, good catch.
OK,
it doesn't if if it doesn't match or the
latest and we update the detail to OK, OK,
Ria are we good like I,
I have explicitly added this as a
separate point because we have to
implement this first time incremental
load, this is handling differently.
We are here we are handling differently
for sourcing started in case of first
time incremental load it we would be
getting the value from the batch friends
OK For the other scenarios OK let's the
possible success.
So in the post load success we have,
we have few parts.
I think four or five would be there.
55 we have 5 S 1st 1 is loading RA
referential integrity records from the
temporary table to the actual main table.
Before loading it cheques whether the
records are all already exist in the main
RA table.
If they do,
those records would be skipped.
OK, so for example,
in the fasting there fire records were
processed already in the second run out
of like we have we got another five RA
records out of those three are already
like 3 are already processed or like
loaded into main array table as part of
our issue our issue then in in the second
day on the second day we won't be loading
the same 3 records again into the main
array table.
OK, this is what so one question here.
So for this RI it is right.
Suppose this record has like like today
I'm seeing one record is not populated OK
into the main table.
When we are loading it into the main
table from the right table then like are
we updating any status to like update it
or anything in the main right table.
So in case of reprocessing,
whenever we find the match in this parent
table then yeah we are updating the main
array table column which is called
processor flag as Y We'll update it as Y
Defaultly whenever we make entries,
it would be null.
Once it gets processed,
we will be updating it with Y even after
like even in the next run onwards,
only the codes with the process to flag
null would be construed for reprocessing.
OK,
that is part of source qual fair query
again source to stage 1 and then job role
error detail table load to job role error
data table.
For job role error detail table load,
we'll use the job ID to identify all the
active job role assignment ID.
It then cheques the error details in the
job role error detail timetable at source
record level and then loads them into job
error detail table and record and column
level.
You got this right.
We will have every record and once we
will just transpose each and every record
into column level in the job error detail
table.
This information captures source database
schema, table column error name, error,
error column value,
source recorder identifier,
rule ID rule a segment ID and error
severe to if all these details would be
fetched from this and if the if the data
comes from multiple source labels,
the source record identifier is stored in
a yeah,
if the source record identifier whatever
the like if the record is coming from
multiple source labels,
then in that case we have to populate the
source record value as a source column
source one column,
source source one value OK and pipe
symbol.
This is what the primary key, right?
Yeah, yeah,
we would be passing primary key value,
right?
Yeah.
If we have multiple sources,
then in that case every table will have
its own like you don't want UUID column,
right.
So that column would be would be pass it
in this format source one column value,
column value like this separated by pipe
symbols and cause column and value would
be separated by Colin.
OK and then coming to George operal
execution log,
it finds all the entries in the job roll
execution log with start status for the
Kibbon job run ID.
It then cheques the related error entries
in the job roll error table.
Table here would be loading all the
details right All the records from rule
temp to actual error detail table right
here.
It will check how many records are like
routed into this table for each rule
assignment and if no records are
processed,
the status is updated to for past and
execution details are updated in the job
rule execution table.
If error records are found,
the status is updated to fail and error
message with error text and error record
count are updated in the job rule
execution log table.
OK.
In case if it is,
if there are error records,
if there are no error records,
it will be updated to past and
corresponding aggregation details would
be updated error message balance
reconciliation the system.
So one question.
So what is error 1?
So when you're we are transposing it to
like 1 record to multiple records, right?
Basically.
So in that case,
like is that done by using a usable
mapping?
Correct, Correct.
Not.
Yeah, it's a mapping only, not Maplet.
It's a mapping only reusable mapping,
balance reconciliation.
The system fetches all active balancing
metrics for the job from balance
reconciliation metadata using job ID.
So whatever the job balance metrics that
we have in the job in the balance
reconciliation metadata table using our
job ID,
we'll fetch all them and then it it then
calculates the target metrics.
We have already calculated source metrics
and we would be passing it as a input
parameter to this balance reconciliation.
And here in this process it then
calculates the target metrics using the
target expression.
I told you right,
our target expression and target balance
ballot Recon philtre would be pass it
from the parameter file using these two.
This ballot Recon philtre is nothing but
active record kind of OK.
So for type 2 table,
we have to consider only the active
records, right balance reconciliation.
So that Philtre I have applied OK and the
target aggregation expression this is
nothing but it will have all the select
clause expression whatever we have to do
OK and then target table details,
the system compares the source metrics.
The system compares the source metrics
with the target metrics to check whether
there are whether there are balance OK.
If the source and target target metrics
match,
both balancing flag and threshold flag
are set to Y.
If they don't match,
balancing flag is set to north and the
difference is check back next the allowed
threshold.
If it is within the threshold,
then it would be This flag would be Y
threshold flag,
otherwise it would be also N.
All reconciliation results are stored in
balance reconciliation stat along with
job run ID and execution run ID and audit
columns OK.
OK, next coming to job run stats.
So here this this whatever this this step
update the job run stats entry with the
final status, source count,
target counts and validation flags.
OK all these things it will update.
First it will it fetches the source
record count and target and change record
count from the job run stress timetable.
This is snowflake table.
OK, if DQ cheques are, if DQ,
if DQ checking is enabled,
it calculates total error records,
critical records and informational
records from the job rule error detail
table.
OK,
how many record total error records are
there?
How many critical error records are there?
How many informational record all these
counts it will check and then if amount
balancing if there are any balancing
metrics are there then it calculates the
number of metrics that are out of
threshold,
number of metrics that are out of balance
but within threshold like that it will do
2 calculations.
System then calculates target insert
record count, target update record count,
target delete record count that will OK
delete reverse.
It don't do any calculation.
It is directly set it to 0 using OK
insert record count, update record count,
RA record count would be calculated using
target table details and RA table details.
It's like so in case suppose no record
has been inserted or updated like will it
update it to 0 or it will be remain it
will remain as one, OK.
If it is not updated,
then in that case it not updated.
Not not updated.
Yeah.
Suppose I got in the run it there was no
record.
Yeah, yeah.
If there are no record,
then it would be updated to CU.
OK, OK.
And then it updates and if it if there
was a report but not like process fully
in that case it will be null.
No,
no update record count is updated to 0.
Like if it is just job it it didn't reach
to the job post but then also it didn't
do it one minute.
So what is your question?
Could you please come again?
Suppose job the next job got failed in
the job load.
It still got somewhere due to some
network.
It would be null.
Then it would be null, yes.
Then the system calculates the record
count balancing flag.
If source and target aggregated some both
are equal then it would be a.
Why else it would be OK and here while
calculating while taking the SO target
records also it is taking target inset
record con, target update, record con,
target critical error record con and
target RA record con and target unchanged
record con.
Cause the condition is not made the flag
is set to end.
It updates the the flags as below
critical error check flag.
It updates the critical error check flag
as Y if there are no critical error
records and then if there are any
critical error records if X like it would
be updated with X if there if there are
no DQ cheques assigned to that job.
And same goes with informational records.
If there are any informational cheques,
why if no one in informational records
then N that no informational DQ cheques
assigned X balance reconciliation Y.
So if all balance metrics are within
threshold then it is Y if any if N if all
balance metrics are out of threshold and
out of X if there are no balance metrics.
OK, why it would be?
Why in both the cases if all are balanced
and if if metrics are out of balance but
within threshold,
then it would be why if the record if the
metrics are out of balance out of
threshold and if there are no metrics
assigned to that job,
then X OK and then how the final this
these three steps tells us how the final
status gets updated in the job restarts.
The status in the job restart is is
updated to fail and an entry in the OK if
this like OK,
so if the current if the record count,
source record count and target aggregated
sum count.
If both doesn't balance these,
I'm telling you the scenarios where the
status is updated,
status in job run stats is updated to
fail and whenever any failure happens,
entry would be made into the job error
stats.
So similarly here also entries being made
into errors job error stats.
So I'm telling you the scenarios whenever
our source record count and have get
record count doesn't match whenever there
is any balancing metrics that is outside
the allowed threshold or if any critical
DQ check fails.
In these three scenarios,
our job runs fast.
Scenario 1 is when like out of threshold
and two is critical error 1030 source
record count and target and change record
count.
So basically we would be checking right
source record if my record count
balancing flag is N then in that case so
in the record count balancing flag we
would be comparing the source record
count against the aggregated sum of
target record count target insert update
error right?
That summation would be a compared
against the source record count right?
So if that is not matching,
then also we would be updating the status
as failed, OK.
And if the the the status in the job
ranks would be updated to success and a
warning notification is sent.
In following cases,
if there are any informational cheques
failures or if any balancing metric is
out of balance but within threshold.
In these cases a warning notification
would be sent.
The status in the IT would be updated to
success and sets success.
Notification would be sent only if all
the record counts balance.
All the balancing metrics are completely
balanced.
All the critical and informational
cheques are passed.
In this case it will be updated to pass
job post load failure.
So basically when any.
This is used when the when any load fails,
When the main load or your post load
success fails,
OK main main stage load or main target
load, OK stage load target load,
your post load success.
Anything fails it it it will be executed
or it it has only two steps.
First it will update the first assist
like it it updates the records in the job
role execution log and in job run stats.
So here in the job role execution log,
it tries to find all the entries in the
job role execution log for the given job
run ID with starter status.
This is the same component, right?
Yeah.
These two are the same components mapping.
At the mapping level,
these two are the same components,
but at the task flow level,
we have separate component for preload
failure and post load failure.
Because I told you right that
notification tasks are different and
handling of those things are slightly
different.
Mostly notifications are different job
preload failure and job post load failure.
OK, that's it.
Yeah,
let me go through this flow chart 50
diagram.
OK, job pre job posting right?
So here once this job job load is done,
we'll just load the RA reports from
temporary to main array.
If there are any DQ cheques I sent to our
job,
we'll load the records from the job role
error detail, time to job,
actual job role table.
If there are any DQ,
check if there are any error records.
The based upon the count of error records,
the status and error log or execution
details will be updated in the job rule
execution log.
If there are any balance metrics or the
present for this particular table,
then this balance sheet cancellation
would be would be happened.
It will just fetch the source related
metric information from the Snowflake
balance sheet cancellation stats
timetable and using target expression and
target philtre condition.
It will get the IT will get the IT will
try to calculate the target metrics and
it will compare both of them with both of
them are like it will come back the
difference between those two values.
If the out of balance value equal to 0,
then it will update the balancing flag to
Y and threshold flag to Y in balanced
cancellation balance to cancellation
stats.
Otherwise if if it is not balanced,
if it is not equal to 0,
then it would be balanced flag would be
updated to north.
After that we will check within the given
whether the difference out of balance
value is within the threshold.
If it is within the threshold.
It will update the threshold flag as well
and otherwise it will update the
threshold flag as and after that it after
that it updates the balance refund flags.
OK so next it here we are just telling
about the flags basically flags how we
are updating in the job run stats.
So here they how we are updating this
balance flag and how we are updating the
balance like we are just telling this
here we have kept it here and after that
here we have just kept the information
related to source record count,
target record count and informational
flags and balance record flag.
How all the flags count statuses are
being updated in the job table and if any
if there is any mismatch and like if
there is any mismatch between the source
and target record counts then we are
updating the record count balancing flags
as if there is any mismatch and if they
are exactly matching why for a given job
run ID based upon the status and flags.
Like I told you right,
there are three scenarios failed,
completed, completed warning,
completed success.
So all these things.
So in case if we have both the issues
like if we have both informational issue
and critical issue.
So majorly it is a failure, right.
So we would be passing both the details,
warning details,
all the datas under failure notification
only under the same failure notification,
we'll be sending out all the details,
failure details,
warning details and that's it.
I'll just cover this like here.
It it,
it's nothing If the if all the jobs under
that batch is succeeded,
then it will update the status to
completed and there is it will update the
status to fail in either in either
scenario,
it will send out the notification
corresponding notification either success
notification or failure notification.
OK, that's it.
Batch word is just simple thing.
That's why I just I have just covered.
Here only,
but if we have any OK here also,
it's it's a small thing only it cheques
the weather of all the actually a batch
load next take it for tomorrow only.
I'm not a simple,
but this post load is huge, right?
OK.
And also like tomorrow along with the
batch post load see,
I can like entirely I can go through the
entire state right and get something with
this and I can discuss on like on the
same day.
Yeah, you were saying something.
Discuss those.
And also your voice is breaking.
OK.
It got disconnected.
Got disconnected.
Give me one minute.
Let me log up now if you are able to hear
me right.
Yeah.
So actually what I'm trying to tell you
is I'll tell you once batch post load is
also done,
I'll just complete the remaining part in
the LLD also, OK.
After that I'll give you a walkthrough of
the mail that I'm telling right.
Whatever the changes that are there and
what are the things that needs to be
implemented and that needs to be followed
or what they're like.
I got it, I got it.
Everything that needs to be what I'm
saying.
So today, like as per the plan,
today you complete the job post with OK.
And tomorrow you complete the batch post
load so that I can like tomorrow I can go
to the batch post load as well as the
entire thing that we discussed, right?
Because we, we like, I saw it bit by bit,
piece by piece, right, if everything.
So I want to go through the entire flow
as well.
Are we disconnected?
Yeah, OK.
Like that is very, very small topic.
It doesn't even take 5 minutes.
That is the reason why I'm trying to
cover two things that that needs to be
like taken care in case of ABC framework.
And also there are things that I want to
inform you.
I'll inform all those things and related
statuses, everything, tracker everything,
I'll inform everything.
So tomorrow and the day after tomorrow
again we'll have the reverse KD right
then after going end to end flow.
If you have any questions we can discuss
and then we'll add the like
implementation related changes as well.
That seems to yeah, that is pending.
Yeah, you yeah, you will be taking care,
right?
Yeah.
But we can discuss like one give give a
thought from your end how to do this,
that OK.
For that we will discuss and we can do
that.
OK.
Yeah,
that that session like let's do it on
Wednesday.
So everything will be covered I guess by
then.
OK, OK, OK.
What?
Which task?
I was a broker,
I guess Broker no account I was taking.
Yeah, yeah,
broker something let me take account.
I,
I guess yesterday I took a broker account
party.
I think actually we were discussing on
account party address.
But that that day I want to show you
balance reconciliation part, right?
That is the reason why I showed that.
But today we can go with account party
address only because you posted all the
but they're like will that have the
balance for installation limited?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Post component.
OK, OK.
That is so common that is reusable.
Now after job load,
we have job post load 1st is RA2 main
array.
This is developed by Bharat,
but I'll try to explain you.
If if we were not able to figure out
anything here, we can reach out to him,
we can pull him.
OK so this is the first city inside this
we have one select close and inside that
we have another subway.
So let's come from the sub query.
So here we are trying OK here we are
trying to get we are we are fetching few
records from temporary table and here we
are doing a lateral pattern on a chill
table and we are trying to get input.
Let me let me open this snowflake.
How this chill looks in main array?
How it got changed?
OK,
so child is this so they're doing a
lateral,
they're doing a lateral pattern on this
child table and they're getting the value
from it and that value they're.
So when we do a lateral pattern on a
Jason text, we'll have key and value,
right?
Yeah,
key they are taking it as a zone 1 table
and value as zone 1 UAD value.
So if you see if you see here,
whatever the key is there,
right First key this they are taking it
as a what is this?
As a German table, German table name,
this is the German table name and they
are taking the value this is the whole
value for F and in that F this is the
like this you,
they are considering it the value as U.
Here they are again doing the lateral
pattern on the test and they're
considering it as AU under that U,
whatever the value they have this value
they are considering as a zone when you
get a value.
OK, OK, And then they are doing a row,
row number partition by job ID.
They're doing a partition by using job ID,
table name, source table name,
and one UUID parted by audit creating
date.
OK, They're just applying version.
So they're just checking if there are any
duplicate records.
If there are any duplicate records,
they are just keeping it.
They're just keeping only one version,
that's it.
They're just taking table name,
UUID value and all the details from the
temp table here.
They're what they're doing is using these
job ID.
They're just taking only one value, Yeah.
And after that in this main array,
they're trying to get the zone to job ID,
zone to table name and zone 1 table name.
All these things from the main array
table using target zone to table name and
process flag is is null.
So whatever the records that are present
in the main array table with process flag
equal to north the null,
they are taking only those records.
After that they're doing the all the
things here.
So they're just joining temper and main
array based upon the job ID,
target table name and this, this OK,
they're doing this full join.
They're doing full join based upon that
they're comparing each and flagging
they're they're flagging each record.
No change,
insert and update if there if if there is
no change in the record.
So they have done this right.
So if the if they found a record where
it's the doc is and main like can you
Scroll down what is pimp and what is mean
here We have parameterized even the
tamper a table earlier they were not sure
about the table name as well.
So that is the reason why I parameterized
it.
This table name is is what like it is the
RI table name or tamper table,
TEMPRA table.
This is the table name.
So for in snowflake,
in snowflake both are in snowflake tamper
and main array both are in snowflake.
They look like this.
What is the purpose of these two?
So these are related to referential
integrity records.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean I think the during during the
stage load we would be loading all the
records which are having are issues into
the timetable and after that they we
would be loading it into temp to main are
tables.
So this temporary table basically works
like we will be like whenever we are
loading in records into the temporary
table we would be deleting the records
from the for that particular job ID which
are loaded as part of the previous run.
So every time it's it's kind of a clean
up based upon the job ID table.
So as we have to reprocess them every
every time.
In the source qualified query we are
having two separate tables one time 1
main.
So main table will have the final truth
how many records are processed processed,
how many records are are still remained
unprocessed.
All those details will have the main main
tables.
This temporary table we are just using to
load that records.
So that will use this table to update the
the main array table otherwise inserted
if there are if,
if they if the old record,
if the record in the main array table.
So for the first time,
all records would be inserted, right?
Yeah, into main,
into temporary table and then from
temporary to main array,
all records would be inserted.
On day 2,
we found that three records like on day 2,
we'll use this main array table for
reprocessing in the stage table though.
So while this reprocessing 2 of the
records are are found their parent parent
record and they are processed OK,
they are processed into the stage table.
So in that case and whatever the three
records OK, 3 records are processed right,
two or two left.
So along with stage 2,
there are two more new records OK.
All these 4 records are routed to
temporary using.
Before loading into this temporary
whatever the records that are loaded
yesterday fire records would be first
deleted and these 4 records would be
inserted OK Using these 4 records,
yesterday's spy records are there right
out office three are processed.
So we didn't find those records in this
in these timetable,
then they would be updated,
OK and then updated like updated in the
sense their process flag would to mark as
Y, OK.
And then newly coming 4 records like new
coming 2 records would be directly
inserted.
And whatever the records that are
processed yesterday that are already
loaded into this main array table
yesterday, they would be ignored.
OK, kind of no change again.
On day three,
all those 4 records would be reprocessed
again like that.
This process continues.
I've like I, I'm thinking like you,
you asked why the necessity of two tables.
That's why I'm explaining why 2 tables
are required.
You got it right.
Yeah, to some some extent I got it.
But we do think that, yeah, if you,
if you go to go through the code, right.
So if we don't have another table,
intermediate temporary table,
it would be difficult to do these updates
and difficult to handle this reprocessing
if we don't have a temporary table.
OK, OK, yeah,
because whatever the request processed
won't won't be coming to tamper A again.
They will be directly routed to stage.
How do we know that they were not they
were already processed.
We would we would get to know only
through tamper A table as the records
that are not present in the tamper A
table for this job ID we are assuming OK,
the at least three records have got
processed.
OK,
these are we have to mark it as processed
like that it will understand.
I think this is the way they designed the
logic to populate like RA records into
the main table.
There are so many ways to handle the
scenario.
This is the way they have implemented OK
and during source to stage load and as I
remember it also takes the main ARRI
table, right?
They can that's good.
So on day one we have fire records, right?
It will all the fire records are with
process flag net using that philtre and
job ID and something Wagga Wagga philtres,
they will again try to check zone ID
whether that particular using that zone
ID,
they will fetch the record again from the
source along with the incremental data.
They will fetch the records using this
zone ID again if they even though if they
are not part of our incremental load,
even yesterday's load,
they will pick along with these two.
So now for those records we will check
whether the parent ID is there or not.
If it is there then we will route that
record to the stage channel.
If it is not then again they will be
routed to tamper once they came tampering
whether they will be handled as this.
Otherwise if the if the records are not
present in tampering but present in main
array then they would be updated as
process.
OK so first we are getting information
from temporary and also main array only
records which with the process tag is
null.
We were taking and here the flag logic is
implemented in such a way they are using
this job ID not equal to main job ID.
All these are exactly same zone 1 you
already same everything is same then it
is of no change after that for insert job
ID is not null so zone two job ID OK we
have one job ID in not null but and we
have all the details.
So what does it mean is we we have all
the details from the temporary table.
The corresponding table details are not
present in the main table.
That means whatever the zone you zone
when right zone,
when you are using the zone,
when you are adding we have one recording
temporary that record if we don't find in
the main record,
we are just directly inserting it.
And after that we don't have the
recording temp table but we have the
recording main table.
Then we are doing an update.
OK, got it.
OK, then yeah, that's it.
Here they were doing.
That's it.
So using these time update and insert
flags,
they are just making inserts and updates
into this table.
Can I go back to the query one?
I mean please no, no, no, Scroll down,
down.
OK so here they are taking only records
with process flag is null right?
So if the records that are already
present like here and there both are
exactly same then they're ignoring.
If temp is having record and main is not
having record then they are doing
inserting.
If temp is not having that record,
main is having that record.
That means it is already processed.
So they are updating the processed flag
as well.
OK,
so here router we have insert flow and
update flow.
In the insert flow,
I'll show you the mapping.
So I don't know why this is not mapped.
I don't know the sequence like
significance of this sequence.
Also,
they're just mapping all the like they're
just loading what are the records they
have in the temporary table to this table.
That's it, OK.
And after that, they're in the update.
They're using columns like zone one job
ID and zone 1 UUID for updating purpose
and they're updating the using zone 1.
All these are just related to like just
like a condition like join condition.
They were just using these these these
fields.
They're using these fields to update this
particular processing field.
Processing flag and audit columns are
updated.
Yes process flag logic to be healthy see
here.
Process flag logic is also there.
If the change flag is update then it is
set as Y else it is not.
Because I I missed this and all the ABC
components are OK I told it.
I'll tell you then.
So if any of these components are failed
it will be routed to job post load
failure.
This is job related.
So here we have two targets 1 is the one
is from AS as I have two here because my
job rule added detail is from Snowflake
and job rule assignment is from Aurora.
Both are from two different databases.
That is the reason why we have two
sources here.
Let me show you the logic for job retail
time.
What is the information that we are
getting from there?
So here we're we're doing like here we
are fetching the records from the job
role error detail temple table and error
description will be there right?
So we are doing a lateral pattern on the
table and using that.
So all the like in error description we
would be loading the details in such a
way that so fast we would be adding
target column then source column so then
error column value then rule 80 then
error code.
This is the way that we have loaded our
source records into the data detail time
right source detail details.
So we are just doing a lateral pattern
and getting all these details after that.
So here we are just considering only our
current run and where the error
description is not null and this OK after
that here OK all the all the things that
we have here are related to this error
and all the other details.
That's it.
How does it look like when you run query
from this particular output of this?
I think we don't have any errors,
but I'll show you in the OK query.
How does it work?
OK, I'll show you in the UT documentary.
Let me open it in the.
So yeah here if you see this result we
have job rule already till 10 with load
is loaded with two records.
OK so 2 records are having the issue.
OK the source aggregated text it it
updated in a wrong way it is so the
columns are not proper.
I get the call.
Actually, once this component is done,
like if we have my lunch and don't Hello.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
OK, we get this.
Is this created in time schema first but
later it's not.
Sure, what's wrong?
OK,
so there if you see the second second one,
this source error text or source
description oh,
this one here error description is there
right.
So in the error description column we
have the values like this.
So which are separated by;
In the sense if we have multiple columns,
which are OK here,
if we have multiple call rule assignments,
then if we have those those those cheques
failure and a single source record,
then we'll be having all those related
information separated by;
So first like when I do the error
description split using the;
Then it is err.
So err err value itself is an 1 error
item OK.
And then after that, each value,
whatever the value that we have.
So once we separate it, so this is 1, uh,
err, this is 1 err, this is 1 err.
So this way we'll,
there will be each value in the in this
record to populate into these columns as
separate columns.
OK,
we we are just doing a split using the
pipe symbol 1st.
We are just doing a lateral phantom when
as we have three separate job rule
assignments, these three would be oh,
sorry, there is, there's a network list.
Sorry.
Oh my God, disconnect.
That's connecting again.
So first,
what I what what I'm what I mean to say
is for each record,
if we have if I have multiple rule
assignment,
first it is doing a lateral pattern based
upon the; So using the;
Each rule assignment,
for each rule assignment, we'll have one,
one entry.
So as I showed in the example,
there are three rule assignments which
are failed for a single record.
So that will be transpose it 2-3 separate
records after transpose 2-3 separate
records using that value.
It we're using the each part of the value
to populate corresponding values like
target column name,
source column and source value.
Like that we would be using and we would
be populating.
So the table you were showing that was
the source table for this table.
Sorry, what table?
Source table job rule error detail temp
Yes,
this is the source table for job rule
error detail.
See here job rule error retail OK and
after that like using all these records
and in the mapping if you go to the
mapping we have another source query
where we are trying to pull all the job
rule assignment.
So we have we have to assign the job rule
assignment ID for each and every column
based upon the column name we would be
assigning the job rule assignment value
OK.
So here from the job rule assignment
table using the job ID and add to philtre
we are bringing all the job role IDs and
target column name and error message text
and job role assignment ID.
All these like these two are used to
populate current time stamp values.
OK, once we bring all these things,
we have a here we have one expression for
for rule ID,
we're just as all the things are
concatenated.
This rule ID would also be like a a
string, right?
So we are just casting it to a begin.
After that we have a joiner where we'll
be joining using rule ID and target
column name.
Using rule ID and target column name we
are doing a join with that records coming
from this job will end this after that
source error text.
So we are having the source error text
like this error message text error value
like this it will like.
I'll show you how it looks.
This looks like this null values found
error column value.
Here you see as I have passed only like I
haven't hard coded that null.
It is giving like this empty string.
So that is the reason why I pass her null
thereafter.
So it would have like this from onwards
but it is not there in like at that time.
OK we are making insert.
We are loading records into both job
snowflake job related table and also
snowflake snowflake and both we we won't
delete any record from the job rule error
detail table from both databases.
OK.
Whereas in ETL source data addition
source window before loading into
snowflake table we would be deleting the
data for that particular job ID.
Even in the other timetables we will be
doing the same.
Whereas for job rule error detail table
it's kind of a permanent table.
We won't be deleting any entries for the
job ID from this snowflake table.
OK, that's it.
OK,
we can discuss post lunch that the
confidential can stop there.